http://www.basscentre.com.au/pages/privacy-policy

Info
Who are we?
Info
Who are we?
Privacy Policy
At The Bass Centre, we are committed to ensuring the privacy of your information. We understand that as a customer using the The Bass Centre website how important the privacy of your personal information is to you. The following statement addresses relevant privacy issues for the The Bass Centre. However, if you have any further questions relating to this privacy statement, please do not hesitate to email us.
Information we collect
For each visitor to our web site, our web server collects the following type of information for statistical purposes:
• The number of users who visit the website,
• The date and time of visits,
• The number of pages viewed,
• Traffic patterns
This is anonymous statistical data and no attempt will be made to identify users or their browsing activities. We use this data to evaluate our website performance and to improve the content we display to you.
When you provide information
The type of information that we collect from you will depend on what products and services you use on the website. When you provide us with personal details i.e. when applying for a The Bass Centre product or online service, we will request personal information such as your name and address, your e-mail address and a contact phone number. This information is important so we may contact you when necessary on issues relating directly to the product or service.
We will not use your personal information for any purpose which is not related to the products or services we provide to you or for any purpose for which you would not reasonably expect us to use the information. Your information may be used by The Bass Centre to enable us to offer you other products and services that will enhance our relationship with you. It is your decision whether you wish us to provide this service to you. We may release information about you where there is a duty to the public to disclose that information. However, we will not sell or disclose your information to any individual or entity outside The Bass Centre, for marketing purposes.
Email Addresses
We may use your email address to send our regular communications which provide information, updates on new services and special offers.
It is our policy to only email customers who give us permission to do so. If we send you an email for a commercial purpose, we will give you the option of not receiving further communications of this nature.
Security of captured data
When capturing customer data it is passed through a secure The Bass Centre server using encryption technology to ensure that your information is protected when being sent over the Internet. This also applies to information that may be collected for The Bass Centre by an agency i.e. when entering a competition, where it will also be passed through a secure server.
Additionally, all stored customer information is protected from unauthorised access through the use of secure passwords and user log ons or other security procedures.
Follow
Privacy policy
Sign up to get the latest on sales, new releases and more…
© 2020 Bass Centre.
This website runs on Shopify
Mastercard
PayPal
Visa
